What is this place?
Where am I?
What was that?
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
Is it true, Aldea?
Did you really see Zeros on Lemuria?
Yes, I saw it with my own eyes.
Why didn't you report that to the brass?
Because I wanted you to
get all the credit, Grabel.
You're a fool...
And one more thing.
That girl who was wearing Zeros
called herself Aine.
Then I suppose we'll have to
do this ourselves.
Episode 7
Imperial Hero -Grabel-
Initiating sealing.
Entrance Magitech signal is dropping.
Ninety, seventy, fifty, thirty...
The Magitech particles
have dropped by 99.999%.
The sealing is complete.
So the data was real?
If we can seal the entrances,
we can drastically alter
the course of this war.
Now we have a way to make...
...the joint US-Japan operation
to retake Okinawa a reality.
But who sent this data to us?
I can't believe that
my first time is with you.
This should be fun!
I just brought you to the cafeteria
because you wanted to try it out.
Don't make it sound like something else.
May we sit across from you, leader?
You're...
I'm never going to forgive you.
The leader of the Masters, Scarlet Fairchild.
Nice to meet you.
Gertrude Baird.
Nice to meet you, asshole.
Sharon Cunningham.
Wh-What are you doing here?
We've joined the academy as well.
For the joint operation, you see.
Hey, Kizuna, I heard you
have a special power.
N-No, it's nothing special.
Now I'm even more interested.
Hey, Kizuna,
can you show me around Ataraxia?
Since we're both the leaders
of our respective teams,
we should get to know each other better.
Enough!
Kizuna has a lunch meeting with me.
Don't interrupt us.
G-Give me a break...
Aine?
Let's go, Kizuna!
Hey, wait!
Okay, Kizuna,
we can't let this valuable afternoon
go to waste.
The only thing going to waste
is all that fat in your boobs!
Uh...
We'll just have to...
...fight for him!
It's on!
Champion!
You guys are ballers!
I'm not done yet!
We're just getting started!
So why are you having a swimsuit contest?
And am I even allowed to be here?
Kizuna!
Here we are!
They're wearing the same swimsuit?
Why are you copying me?
You're copying me!
H-Hey!
Come with me, Kizuna!
Wait!
Well?
My breasts may not be as big,
but my proportions are better, right?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
I told you, I'm interested.
Interested?
Like, the whole Heart Hybrid thing...
What's it like?
Want to try it with me?
Ow...
Don't move!
I'm sorry!
Don't talk!
Is this a Heart Hybrid?
What are you doing?
Listen, Yurishia, it was an accident...
It's fine.
It was silly of me to get
worked up against a child.
Where are you going?
Don't make me say it.
Hey...
Hey, Scarlet.
What?
You and Yurishia are actually
friends, aren't you?
Huh?
You were in perfect harmony
when you were dancing.
And you had basically
the same taste in swimsuits.
No!
That's not true!
Scarlet...
You don't know what a
horrible person Yurishia is!
She...
She used us as pawns to be sacrificed!
Sacrificed?
It was our first time...
...fighting a Dragorie,
a Category-A Magitech weapon.
W-We can't fight this thing!
Help—
Yurishia deliberately sent us on ahead
to fight the Dragorie.
And after she made us wear it down,
she took all the glory for herself.
I'm never going to forgive her!
I'm never going to forgive Yurishia!
I can't believe Yurishia would do that.
She's not that type of person.
Forget it!
I'm going home!
You heard that?
Yes.
Is what she said true?
If that's what she said, it probably is.
Yurishia...
See you tomorrow.
All hail the general!
All hail the Empire!
How dare she act like she's more
important than the Royal Guards?
But I think we should just let her
do what she wants for now.
She's going to trip up eventually.
I know that!
Cheers!
You're getting too excited.
What's wrong with that? It's a celebration.
I'm so hot.
On days like this, it starts to throb.
This scar you gave me...
The same goes for me.
A fragment of your spear is still within me.
Did it hurt? I'm sorry.
Hey!
Grabel...
Stop it...
No.
Aldea...
I know.
I'll get a battleship ready.
One with a long range, right?
Th-That's right.
Then let's get back to it.
No.
N-Now's not the time...
Don't say that.
It's okay, right?
N-No...
You're so mean, Grabel.
Captain, I made this in Home Ec!
Please share it with everyone!
Thanks!
It's good.
I'm sure you'll make a
good wife someday, Sylvia.
A-A wife?
N-No, it's too sudden!
I'm still not old enough to marry,
but if it was with you...
Did you say something?
Bye!
Why?!
Why can't I find anything?
It's me I'm looking up!
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
What am I?
There you are, Aine.
What are you doing in here?
I'm free to go wherever I want.
What are you doing here?
Sylvia made us some cookies.
Want some?
I don't need any.
But...
I said no!
You do need some.
Why aren't you saying anything?
About what?
Don't play dumb.
There's something you want to ask me, right?
I don't want to ask about something
you don't want to talk about.
But, if you ever do want to talk about it,
come straight to me.
Kizuna.
Kizuna...
I...
Give me a sitrep!
How many enemies?
It's...
It's a woman!
It's a single, unarmed woman!
You, from the other dimension!
Surrender, bitch.
I'm impressed you were willing
to come here yourself,
but it was a stupid thing to do.
Bored now.
Can I shoot her?
Not yet, whore.
I am General Grabel,
Commander of the Batlantis Empire's
Lemuria Theater 6th Expeditionary Force.
I demand you hand over Zeros
and its Magitech knight.
Now.
Otherwise I cannot guarantee your safety.
What? Are you crazy, slut?
You're surrounded by the enemy.
Bite it, alien.
Negotiations failed, then?
A-All units, engage!
Zoros.
Hurry!
What happened?
Gertrude? Sharon?!
Come in!
That's...
Gertrude! Sharon!
Deploy!
Wait! You can't just attack without a plan!
Shut up!
What is this?!
It's so powerful!
Kizuna...
It's my fault this happened to you...
Forget about me.
Where's everyone else?
Himekawa... Aine...
Both of you get back!
I can't let you handle this!
Piss off!
Are you going to fight with no ammo?
Blades!
You're mine!
Gunsword...
Raver.
You may be proud, Knight of Lemuria.
You made me use my Gunsword.
I'm going to hit you hard.
The Kuros, huh?
Go!
Bullet!
No way... She was able to stop
a full-power attack from the Kuros?
No!
Everyone...
How dare you?!
Stop it!
Come.
I'll take out a wimp like you with one hit.
Take this!
Wait!
I won't let you touch Aine.
You're...
...a man?
Wiped out...
Amaterasu has been wiped out!
Kizuna...
I see.
Do you know who you are?
If you want to know, come with me.
Don't touch her.
We'll see each other again,
male Magitech knight.
Get the recovery teams out there!
Hurry! No wasting time!
She let them go?
Welcome back.
I'm almost out of magic, too.
Being on Lemuria uses more
of my magic than anticipated.
But...
Next time, I will succeed.
What was that...
Kizuna!
Illustration: Yoshihiro Watanabe
I swear by the honor of Batlantis,
and my pride as a soldier,
I shall have victory!
Come on, Grabel, let's take
up where we left off...
And that Zeros...
Oh, you're so silly, Grabel...
Connective Hybrid
S-Stop it, Aldea!